(Penny:)Too bad.
- You're going up Euclid Avenue?
- Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)Leonard takes Los Robles Avenue.
(Penny:)Well, good for Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Euclid Avenue is shorter as the crow flies,
but it has speed bumps...
...which increase point-to-point drive time,
making it the less efficient choice.
(Sheldon:)But you have the con.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Sheldon:)If you're not going to slow down for
the speed bumps, I withdraw my objection.
(Sheldon:)Here's a fun question.
(Sheldon:)Do you know
what the most common street name is?
(Leonard:)- No.
- The answer's tricky.
(Sheldon:)It's Second Street.
(Sheldon:)You'd think it would be First Street.
(Sheldon:)In most towns, First Street eventually
gets renamed to something else.
(Sheldon:)Like Main Street...
(Sheldon:)...Broad Street...
(Sheldon:)...Michigan Avenue.
(Sheldon:)Leonard and I
often use our commute time...
(Sheldon:)...to exercise our minds
with brain teasers like that.
(Sheldon:)We also play games.